Let's continue with a conceptual RNN example.
我们继续学习概念意义上循环神经网络的示例
Assume that we want to build a sequence detector,
假设我们想要构建一个序列检测器
and let's decide that our sequence detector will track letters.
我们决定时序检测器可以追踪字母
So we will actually build a word detector.
所以实际上我们构建了词语检测器
And more specifically, we want our network to detect the word, Udacity.
具体来说 我们希望网络检测到词语 优达学城 (Udacity)
Just the word.
只是这个词语
So before we start,
在我们开始前
we need to make a few decisions.
我们需要做出几个决定
We can define the input by using a one-hot vector encoding,
通过使用 one-hot 向量编码定义输入
containing seven binary values.
包括 7 个二进制值
Here, I use the letters in ascending order, but that's arbitrary.
这里我使用的字母按照升序方式 不过字母的顺序可以是任意的
Each letter will be represented by one in the index it corresponds to,
每个字母都用对应的指标 1 表示
and zeros everywhere else.
其他地方都是 0
So for example, the letter A will be represented by one followed by six zeros.
例如 字母 A 用 1 和六个 0 进行表示
Here are the rest of the letters that we need.
这是我们其余需要的字母
The letters not appearing in the word Udacity can be
没有出现在词语优达学城 (Udacity) 的字母
addressed by a simple vector containing all zeros,
通过一个全部包括 0 的简单向量表示
like these letters, for example.
例如这些字母
The sequence we are trying to detect will be of length
我们希望检测的序列会是
seven with inputs in the following order: U,
长度为 7 的输入 顺序如下 U
D, A, C, I,
D A C I
T, and finally, Y.
T 和 Y
We can train the system by feeding it random letters at each timestep.
我们在每个时间步长添加随机字母 训练系统
Creating a sequence of inputs demonstrated here from left to right.
这里展示了从左向右创建输入序列
Occasionally, we will also insert the word Udacity.
我们也会偶尔插入词语优达学城 (Udacity)
We set the target values,
我们设置目标值
the outputs to zero all the time except for when
输出总为 0
the last letter Y of the sequence Udacity enters the system.
除非优达学城 (Udacity) 最后一个字母 Y 进入系统
Only then, the target will be set to one.
只有那时 目标值设为 1
Again, the system will acknowledge all inputs and will respond with
另外 系统会承认所有输入
a target output of one only when the desired sequence is detected.
并且只有检测到满意序列时 才会返回目标输出 1
Sketching our network in an unfolded form,
我们以展开形式绘制网络的概略图
we have an input vector of seven values,
我们得到一个包含 7 个值的输入向量
a single output, and a state.
一个输出和一个状态
The state can have any number of hidden neurons.
状态可以是包含任何数量的隐藏神经元
In this illustration, we will use n to leave things generic.
在这个图解中 我们使用 n 更具有通用性
The first state vector is usually set to zero,
第一个状态向量通常设为 0
allowing the next state to evolve as inputs come in.
这样下一个状态可以成为接下来的输入
When training the network,
训练这个网络时
we set the targets to either zero or one.
我们把目标值设为 0 或 1
The target will be zero when the word Udacity is not detected,
没有检测到优达学城 (Udacity) 这个词语时 目标为 0
and one when it is.
如果检测到 目标为 1
If we train our system on targets that are either zero or one,
如果按照目标为 0 或 1 训练系统
we expect that the output will also take on values between zero and one.
我们希望输出也会在值 0 到 1 之间
After training our system and optimizing the weights,
训练系统和最优化权重后
we would expect that when the sequence Udacity appears,
我们希望出现序列 Udacity 时
the output will signal that a sequence has been
输出会通过呈现值接近 1
detected by taking on a value close to one,
提示检测到了序列
like 0.9 in this case.
例如这个例子中的 0.9
Practically speaking, we can set a threshold of, say, 0.9,
实际上来说 我们可以设置阈值 如 0.9
and decide that whenever the output exceeds this threshold value,
确定如果输出超过这个阈值
the sequence of interest has been detected.
可以检测到我们想要的序列
The number 0.9 in this case, by the way,
顺便说一下 这个例子中
was selected as an arbitrary example.
值 0.9 是任意选择的
In our example, the RNN was trained to recognize sequences of seven inputs,
在我们例子中 循环神经网络经过训练 识别包含 7 个输入的序列
like the letters in the word Udacity.
例如优达学城 (Udacity) 这个词语的字母
However, we could have trained the RNN to recognize
不过我们可以训练循环神经网络
sequences of letters that have a different lengths,
识别其他长度的字母序列
like five in the word happy.
例如快乐 (happy) 词语中的 5 个字母
Generally speaking, the RNN can deal with varying sequence lengths.
一般来说 循环神经网络可以处理各种各样的序列长度
So, how do we train this network?
那么我们如何训练这个网络呢？
Or in other words,
换句话说
how do we optimize its weights to minimize the output error?
我们如何优化它的权重 来最小化输出误差呢？
We do that using backpropagation through time,
我们要利用通过时间的反向传播 实现这一点
and we'll be learning all about that in the next set of videos.
我们会在接下来的视频中学习所有这些内容